Arpit Agrawal

Salesforce Developer

Contact

Address

Jaipur, RJ 302039

Phone

887 576 1723

E-mail

Arpitagarwal663@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://bit.ly/arpitlinkedin

Trailhead

https://www.salesforce.com/trailblazer/arpitsfdc97

Skills

C++, Java, Apex, HTML, CSS, Java Script, SOQL, SOSL, Salesforce Flows, Apex Test Classes, Apex Triggers, Reports, Dashboards, Salesforce Admin, LWC, LWC Components.

Languages

Hindi

Upper intermediate

English

Upper intermediate

Salesforce Developer with over 2 year of experience in building, testing, iterating and deploying changes supporting technical maintenance, ongoing enhancement to existing features and new functionality. A proven problem solver with abilities in troubleshooting escalated support issues by performing analysis on root cause and implementing short and long term solutions.

Work History

2021-02 -Current

Salesforce Developer

Techwizard Software Solutions, Jaipur

- Gathered user requirements and support applications design discussion and documentation.
- Developed apex classes, controller classes and apex triggers for various functional needs in the application.
- Developed custom objects, profiles, Sharing rules, roles and integration using web services, as needed by the business.
- Developed Rest APIs to integrate with another systems.

2018-07 -2019-02

Assistant Engineer

Bijson Innovations Pvt. Ltd., Jaipur

- Worked with Project engineer to assist in development, design, and execution of projects.
- Determined budget, manpower, schedule and material needed to successfully execute projects.
- Presented drawings to project managers and incorporated recommended changes.

Education

2022-01 -

MBA: Information Technology

Current

Lovely Professional University - Punjab

2014-07 -2018-06

Bachelor of Technology: Mechanical Engineering

Rajasthan Institute Of Engineering And Technology -Jaipur

Graduated with 72.5% Overall with Honors

2011-05 -	Secondary Education
2012-07	Gandhi Bal Niketan Sr. Sec. School - Jaipur Passed with 59.50%
2013-07 -	Senior Secondary Education
2014-03	Gandhi Bal Niketan Sr. Sec. School - Jaipur
	Passed with 66.00%

Certifications

2016-01	Participated in ethical hacking workshop by IIT Kanpur.
2019-02	Participated in 2 days Workshop on E-waste Management.
2022-09	Certificate of completion of C++ Programming by Samyak Institute
2023-11	Certificate of completion of Java Programming by Samyak Institute
2023-05	Salesforce Certified Associate

Projects

SALESFORCE RECRUITMENT PROJECT

 Basically this project is design to helps the HR to conduct recruitment process and assign positions to hired candidates and to remove the manual creating multiple sheets which consume lot of time and hard work also provide the facility to HR to access the list of candidates and able to select the candidates that fulfill the requirements of the organization.